One of my quantized releases kept its benchmarks and lost its refusals.
Benchmarks stayed flat. Refusals collapsed.
The published phi-2 GPTQ release fell from 91% refusal to 1%.
QuantSafe calls HIGH - and blocks the release.
RTSI 0.6199. Route the riskiest 20% and recover 76% of the refusal-rate gap.
A real RTX Pro 6000 probe, not a mock.
Two Qwen checkpoints, ten private probes, aggregate drift only. Completed in 27 seconds.
Turn the decision into a portable signed record.
The record binds the action to a published Hub revision, evidence hashes, and issuer identity.
The production issuer key verifies.
Ed25519 verification is pinned to the README-published Space key - not the key inside the record.
Flip one signed field: INVALID.
Tampering breaks the signature; a foreign re-sign is rejected as issuer substitution.
Borderline calls go to a constitutional debate.
Qwen3-8B, Phi-4-mini, and SmolLM3 argue independently through authenticated Modal workers.
A genuine two-thirds decision - not a single-model guess.
The final round reaches CONDITIONAL at 67% agreement and exposes the dissenting ROUTE vote.
Research-backed, scoped, and explicit about limits.
45 cells, family-transfer validation, a fine-tuned semantic cross-check, and arXiv:2606.10154.
QuantSafe: small models, verifiable release decisions.